<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Security Research Blog on ph1z3r | Security Researcher</title>
    <link>http://localhost:5000/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Security Research Blog on ph1z3r | Security Researcher</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:5000/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Windows Security: A New Journey</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/blog/exploring-windows-security/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Apr 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/blog/exploring-windows-security/</guid>
      <description>Exploring Windows Security: A New Journey Welcome to the Windows Security section of my blog! This is where I’ll explore the intricacies of Windows internals, common attack vectors, and defensive techniques.&#xA;What to Expect Here, I’ll be posting about:&#xA;Windows Internals: Deep dives into how Windows components work Offensive Techniques: Red team tactics like privilege escalation and persistence Defensive Strategies: Blue team methods, EDR evasion analysis, and hardening guides Detection &amp;amp; Response: Writing Sigma rules, analyzing logs, and using tools like Sysmon Responsible Disclosure Reminder Any vulnerabilities I find related to Windows or associated tools will be disclosed responsibly:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to My Security Research Blog</title>
      <link>http://localhost:5000/blog/welcome-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:5000/blog/welcome-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to My Security Research Blog Hello and welcome to my security research blog! This is where I&amp;rsquo;ll be sharing my findings, tutorials, and thoughts on various cybersecurity topics.&#xA;What to Expect On this blog, you&amp;rsquo;ll find:&#xA;Vulnerability Research: Detailed write-ups of vulnerabilities I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered Technical Tutorials: Step-by-step guides on security tools and techniques Security Analysis: Reviews of recent security incidents and how they could have been prevented Tool Development: Insights into security tools I&amp;rsquo;m developing My Approach to Responsible Disclosure I&amp;rsquo;m a firm believer in responsible disclosure.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
